♪
[JINWOO]
Goto's sitting out.
[scoffs]
Thanks to him
I get to watch some
S-ranks in action though.
[MA DONGWOOK]
Well...
-[grunts]
-[cracking]
♪
Let's kick this thing off.
[grunts]
[thudding]
Testing our brute strength?
Yeah!
Nice and simple!
All right! You're about
to see size does matter!
[yells]
[both grunting]
[gasps]
[LIM TAE-GYU] I can't beat
speedsters in close combat!
-[grunts]
-[thuds]
In case you didn't know,
my specialty is ranged attacks!
[thudding]
Hoshino!
Watch where you're goin'!
Hurry and take him down!
[hollering]
-[thuds]
-[rumbling]
Just checking,
but they have reinforced
this place
with the highest quality
of essence stone,
-right, Chairman Go?
-[laughs] Yes.
I'm thinking
we may have to reevaluate
how sturdy it really is,
though.
[YOONHO] These guys
are the cream of the crop
among S-rank hunters.
I need to approach
this fight like
they're not just trying
to grab my wrists,
but to snap them!
-[gasps]
-[thuds]
[YOONHO]
Atsushi Kumamoto.
Doesn't seem very aggressive
for a combat type.
[deep breaths]
[KUMAMOTO]
Damn it.
I'm not cut out
for this at all.
I just don't have
the heart for it.
♪
[YOONHO]
Is Goto using us?
Seeing if his hunters
are ready to fight the ants?
If that's the idea,
I'm here for it.
[chuckles]
♪
So I'm supposed to be
a test, huh?
Time to see
if you pass or fail!
[KUMAMOTO] Nope!
I'm outta here!
[grunts]
[thuds]
[PARK JONGSOO]
Whatta buncha maniacs.
A little A-rank like me
would get smoked.
No way! You're like the very
definition of pure grit
and plenty tough, too!
-[thudding]
-[rumbling]
[TANAKA] [scoffs]
In terms of physical strength.
Guess I win.
[chuckles]
Who would have thought
I'd be eating the floor?
It's a humbling first for me.
[thuds]
[HOSHINO]
I believe you lose.
[grunting]
Is running your only tactic?
[rumbles]
If you're targeting me
over Hunter Cha.
You must think
I'm the weakest link.
♪
[TAWATA]
I can't predict her moves!
She's equal parts
graceful and deadly.
Now I see
why they call her the Dancer.
It's frighteningly accurate.
[both grunting]
[CHA HAE-IN]
I'd better help Hunter Baek.
[gasps]
♪
[whooshing]
Did you see that?
[CHA HAE-IN]
Oh, no.
I lashed out on reflex!
♪
[growls]
-[groans]
-Aw, hell.
Looks like he snapped again.
[FUJISHIMA]
Yeah.
Which means
all bets are off now.
Do you think
we should intervene?
Not if their lives
aren't in danger, no.
♪
[CHA HAE-IN]
He's fast!
-[grunts]
-[thuds]
-[rumbling]
-Okay, you guys!
This is getting bad!
[thuds]
Uh...
Ah!
[JINWOO]
Sorry to interrupt you there.
But this doesn't feel like
a friendly sparring
match anymore.
[KUMAMOTO]
Who the hell are you?
[grunts]
That's crazy!
He laid out Kumamoto
in his berserk state!
You said this one
is registered as a mage type?
Yes, sir.
That's what I heard, at least.
[GOTO] Might have to confirm
that myself.
[JINWOO] Hunter Cha,
are you good to accept
the loss for this match?
[sighs]
Since Hunter Baek
seems to have
tapped out as well.
[CHA HAE-IN]
Sure.
Hm.
[YOONHO]
Even if I'd gone all out,
the result would've been
the same.
[HANEKAWA]
Hunter Sung.
If you're up for a round.
Guildmaster Goto
would like to challenge you.
[JINWOO]
He's looking for a fight.
Don't need a translation
to know that.
Good.
I've been wanting
to try out the skills I got
from the Demon's Castle.
Is the thought
of facing me funny?
Goto-san.
Good news,
Hunter Sung's agreed
to spar with you.
On one condition, however.
[GOTO]
What's that?
He'll only fight
if you don't hold back on him,
sir.
[chuckles]
Fine by me.
The Jeju Island raid
draws closer,
and all eyes
are on the hunters.
The world is waiting to see
if this alliance with Japan
will be enough
to tip the scales of victory...
[JOOHEE'S MOM]
Joohee, dontcha got work?
[JOOHEE]
I'm off.
Told ya yesterday.
[JOOHEE'S MOM]
Really?
Well, don't slack too much.
Gotta do our best,
just like the hunters
out there are doin'.
[wind blowing]
[dial tone ringing]
Hello.
Um.
I have questions about
the Jeju raid's defense,
if you have time.
[LIM TAE-GYU]
What's happening now?
Guess our renowned tenth
S-rank is feelin' feisty.
He's fixin' to go
head-to-head with Goto.
[CHA HAE-IN] He held his own
in that A-rank dungeon,
but I wonder
how he'll do against
an S-rank hunter?
[YOONHO] Surprised you don't
have your handkerchief.
The smell of hunters
not bothering you?
It's not like I can keep
my nose covered
while I'm on the battlefield.
Should we stop this
before it starts?
A spellcaster going up
against a melee hunter
in close combat.
Normally, I'd say
it's a bad idea.
But I bet I'm thinking
the same thing you are
about this matchup.
Uh?
[YOONHO] And I'm sure my hopes
are just as high.
Because if I'm right,
Hunter Sung has a rare ability
to keep growing stronger.
[sighs]
-Okay. Let's...
-[thuds]
[whooshing]
[JINWOO]
Come on, man.
Not cool.
[GOTO]
He's awfully nimble.
And people think he's a mage?
What a joke.
♪
I'll expose you
for what you really are!
[JINWOO] Oh, yeah,
he's definitely a step above
the other S-ranks.
But I can still dodge him.
[GOTO]
Smiling again?
[LIM TAE-GYU] I'm goin'
cross-eyed trying to keep up.
He's really hangin' in there,
isn't he?
Evading such quick attacks
is very impressive.
[CHA HAE-IN] It's not that
he's "hanging in there,"
though.
He's egging him
on to test his strength.
[grunts]
[GOTO] This whole run around
thing is getting on my nerves.
Change of plans.
I'm going to kill him!
[thwacks]
[grunts]
-[thuds]
-[rumbles]
Is he all right?
Uh?!
[gasps]
Careful with that thing,
someone could've lost an eye.
[GOTO] Is he toying with me
by grabbing my hand?
[speaking in Japanese]
I can only guess
what you just said.
But grabbing your wrist
would end the game.
And neither of us
want it to be over so soon.
[growls]
♪
Our guildmaster's not playing!
At this rate,
both of them are gonna
wind up getting
seriously injured!
[energy blazing]
♪
[both grunt]
[JINWOO] [gasps]
What the?
Hunter Sung!
That's enough!
Goto-san!
This fight's getting
out of hand.
Let's call it here.
While you're both in one piece!
Tell your guild master
this match is over!
Oh. Right!
[YOONHO]
Did I spoil your fun?
[JINWOO]No.
Ha-ha. You fought the great
Ryuji Goto and lived.
All he managed to do
was nick ya once!
Good on ya!
[sighs]
[JINWOO]I got a little
more intense than I meant to.
But...
I have a good grasp
of everyone's skills now.
Sent soldiers into five
of their shadows, too.
♪
[GUNHEE]
Thank you.
Later, I'll send you
the list of hunters
participating in the raid.
[HANEKAWA]
Hm. And forward it
to our vice guild master
too, please.
[GUNHEE]
Take care.
[car engine revving]
[JINWOO]
Chairman Go.
Ah, Hunter Sung.
How can I help you?
So about this Jeju Island raid.
♪
[GOTO]
Reiji.
You'd be shocked by how good
one of these hunters is.
[SUGIMOTO] [laughs]
I doubt he compares
to the guildmaster
of the Drawn Sword.
[GOTO]
Don't be so sure.
[SUGIMOTO]
Which one is it?
Sung Jinwoo.
He's the recently
reawakened S-rank.
Hm.
Okay, that's strange.
I have the list
for the raid here.
But his name's not on it.
It's not?
I don't see Hunter Sung.
I guess he won't be
joining the raid after all.
While it's a shame,
I'm sure he has his reasons.
Either way...
[YOONHO] Byung-gu's name
is missing, too.
Either way...
We've got a solid team
of fifteen S-rank hunters
that are pledged to our cause.
This time's going
to be different.
[grunts]
♪
This time, we'll win!
I'm home.
[JINWOO]
Yeah, about time!
Hey, sweetie.
Dinner's ready.
I'd say your timing's perfect.
Let's eat, then.
[SUNG JINAH]
I'll just go by there later.
[JINWOO] Mom just woke up
from a four-year coma.
She needs me.
Which is why...
I'm not going to Jeju Island.
[wind whooshing]
[water burbling]
[ANT QUEEN]
My subjects need food,
but there is no prey.
They're cannibalizing
each other
to sustain themselves.
This won't do.
We must leave the island.
I need stronger offspring,
more powerful than any other.
Capable of leading
-my mighty queendom.
-[grumbles]
[clatter]
♪
[growls]
[ANT QUEEN] Grow strong,
my son, for all of us!
[roars]
♪
The ant magic beasts
have been evolving
at a disturbing rate.
They only crawled along
the ground
during the first three
Jeju Island raids.
But as you can see
in this recently
captured footage.
They've taken a more
humanoid appearance
in addition to growing
large wings.
In response...
The Hunter's Association
is formulating
a strategy to combat
this newest threat.
♪
[growls]
[BOY 22B] You messed
with the wrong S-rank,
you stupid beast!
[laughing]
This is a bad call
and you know it.
Every hunter was called
to join the defense force,
so why shouldn't I?
Well, Miss Han,
you're an E-rank,
for one thing.
[groans]
So that's how it's gonna be?
[YOO JINHO]
Sorry!
[NEWSCASTER 3A] In the event
any rogue ants
make their way
to the mainland,
hunters of all ranks
are being enlisted
as a countermeasure
to protect civilians.
♪
[GUNHEE]
Tonight, we rest.
Tomorrow, we raid Jeju Island.
[engines rumbling]
[OPERATOR 22A]
This is the first fleet.
We've arrived
at our designated coordinates.
[OPERATOR 22B]
Second fleet here.
We've arrived as well.
[OPERATOR 22C] Third fleet
has eyes on the island
and is now approaching.
[OPERATOR 22D]
Fourth fleet is also en route.
We anticipate arrival
in five minutes.
[YOONTAE] Master, do we have
what it takes to beat the ants?
[JONGSOO] No way of knowin'
for sure until we try.
But we were stationed
here 'cause
we're usin' our smarts
to fight these things, too.
No creepy-crawly's
gonna crawl past me.
You're inspiring!
I'll follow you
for the rest of my life,
however long that might be!
Take care of things here,
Vice Guildmaster.
I'm planning
to just space out.
I mean, we'll be on standby.
[DONGWOOK]
Anything can happen!
Besides, knowing
you're on duty puts me at ease.
I can go into battle
with a clear head.
Tch!
[VICE GUILDMASTER]
Please be careful, sir.
-[DONGWOOK] Will do.
-What?
Why the hell is Minsung
stationed up here?
Do you know
how much he's worth?
I can't have him
getting eaten by ants!
Tell him to hide in the back!
♪
[JINCHUL]
All squads have made contact.
The mainland force,
the coastal guard,
and the team on Jeju.
The diversionary unit
has landed
on the island as well.
Hm.
A heartening turnout.
So many hunters heard
the call to arms
and answered without question.
Including,
a very surprising yet
very welcome addition.
I'm ready, how 'bout you?
[gasps]
♪
-[YOONHO] Byung-gu!
-[chuckles]
Could've sworn
you said you were retired!
[BYUNG-GU]
Yeah, but then I realized,
without a healer you'd be dead
in a matter of seconds.
You see a magic beast
and charge straight in
without thinking
'Cause if I didn't,
they'd make a beeline for you
and tear you to shreds!
[scoffs]
♪
[GOTO]
It's like a ghost town.
Alpha here.
All hunters, sound off.
Team Bravo.
In position.
Charlie here.
Team Delta.
We're ready for action.
[helicopter whirring]
-[YOONHO] A live broadcast?
-Yes. Well, mostly.
There's a ten-minute delay
to edit the intense scenes.
As a cameraman,
it's a true honor to be
documenting this historic clash
for the whole world to see!
[YOONHO]
Sure.
When hunters have something
or someone to protect,
they always up their game.
That said, you do know being
behind that lens
won't keep you safe.
Oh, I'll be okay, sir.
Though you wouldn't
guess it, I'm an A-rank.
I'm used to filming
hazardous stuff.
Well, then, welcome aboard.
This is prob'ly the first time
the public will ever see
a raid like this,
but it might also be the last.
Hell, it had better be.
Let's put a proper
end to this story.
[YOONHO]
If we don't pull this off,
our whole country could be
wiped from the map.
More than ever, we need a hero.
[JINCHUL]
I just got word.
The strike team
is prepared to mobilize.
All right.
This is it.
Let the fourth Jeju Island
raid commence!
Release your full strength!
[ALL]
Roger.
[JONG-IN] The diversionary
unit is making its move.
This bait is really
something else.
There go the ants.
[ants buzzing]
Just had to target
our transport.
[JONG-IN]
Please open the hatch.
I'll handle it.
[door whirring]
[flapping]
[fire roaring]
[blasts]
Amazing.
There are quite
a few of these pests.
So brace yourself
for some turbulence!
[blasts]
♪
[JONG-IN] It's been
a long time, Jeju Island.
But I'm back.
Well, hot damn!
That's our
Ultimate Weapon for ya!
Yessiree!
Let's touch down,
and then make our way
into the cave.
[helicopter whirring]
[DONGWOOK] The Japanese hunters
should be able to distract
the ants for about an hour.
Which means,
we have to get in,
take down the queen,
and get out.
No pressure.
♪
It's the moment of truth,
everyone!
Let's go!
Ready the interference signal.
On my mark, activate.
Transmitting now, sir.
[static sound]
[SUGIMOTO] Good luck having
your minions
detect a distress
signal now, Your Majesty.
-[grunts]
-[growling]
Keep flinching,
and you'll wind up dead!
[grunts]
Why even wait around
for them to execute the queen?
Wouldn't it be a lot faster
if we just killed off
all the ants instead?
Maybe. We could.
-[screams]
-Let's approach it like Kenzo.
-He's having a field day.
-[laughs]
[KEI] Where there's smoke,
there's fire.
Bet it's that Che,
er, Choi guy.
[KEI] If he and I fought,
do you think I could take him?
Fire versus ice.
How original.
[JONG-IN]
The nest is secured.
Let's not waste a single
second they buy us.
[YOONHO] That's a lot
of tunnels to choose from.
Question is, which one of them
is gonna lead us to the queen?
[wind gusting]
[fires]
[explosions]
How about a little
warning next time, Jong-in?
[JONG-IN] We don't have time
to search them all
and we can't divide
and conquer.
But if we're after the tunnel
that leads the deepest
underground.
I believe
that's the one we want.
That's the last
of the daily quest.
Kinda eerie
how no one's around today.
They formed two teams
of S-ranks,
and every member is strong.
It should be an easy victory.
Even without me.
[firing]
[BYUNG-GU] Are we sure
the queen is down here?
She might've abandoned
them to run.
[YOONHO]
It's an island.
There's nowhere she could go.
Hunter Cha and I
found something up this way!
[gasps]
[BYUNG-GU]
It's an egg chamber!
[JONG-IN] So the queen's
chamber should be close.
Look over there!
That egg.
It's huge.
If the queen laid that,
what kind of thing was inside?
Hey, whatever hatched
from that egg
isn't what our team
came here to kill.
Focus on the queen ant.
[YOONHO] I say that,
but it's unsettling.
They keep on evolving.
And if there's an ant
out there
that was born from an egg
of this size...
Damn bugs.
These shitheads mean war.
Got munched pretty good.
You want me
to patch you up there, buddy?
Gotta pay the price, though.
[TANAKA]
Quit being a screwy brat.
Just do it.
Okay, but there's
something that I want.
And, no, it isn't money
this time around.
-I...
-[growling]
More incoming.
Fine.
All right, Shimizu.
Whatever you want, just--
[gasps]